<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-06T22:18:33+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Zeez Blog</title><subtitle>Zhengyu's personal blog. He has multiple passions and interests, and  he likes sharing what he knows.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">It’s High Time We Ended Racism</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/02/high-time-we-ended-racism.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It's High Time We Ended Racism" /><published>2020-06-02T21:29:14+07:00</published><updated>2020-06-02T21:29:14+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/02/high-time-we-ended-racism</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/02/high-time-we-ended-racism.html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“History will have to record that the greatest tragedy of this period of social transition was not the strident clamor of the bad people, but the appalling silence of the good people.”&lt;/strong&gt; ― Martin Luther King Jr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am one of the good people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a good mediator. I am not American but I have traveled in 20 states. I am not black or white. If these don’t make me a good mediator, profile one, and I will help you find them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t say I know about the U.S., but lately, I have been continuously surprised how many ignorant Americans there are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millions of people have been enslaved in America. Without the slaves, many European immigrants would not have survived and thrived on the continent; the U.S. could not have become so developed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Black Lives Matter” is not loud enough. A stronger written expression would be vulgar. Hence the violence. The violence is simply a stronger way to say “Black Lives Matter”. The expression has to be heard and understood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One should never forget that the U.S. has a history of 246 years of institutionalized slavery and the subsequent discrimination of the Jim Crow laws that marked African-Americans as second-class citizens. The formal apology for slavery and Jim Crow issued by the U.S. House of Representatives in 2008 was NOT enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can the U.S. apologize better?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t count on the government. You can’t count on the legal system. But you can count on yourself and your community. Brainstorm about &lt;strong&gt;what you can DO&lt;/strong&gt;, not just say or repost on social media, to apologize for what your European ancestors had done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An apology will never be enough, but keep trying, and be grateful. It wouldn’t be too much to have another Thanksgiving dedicated to the passed slaves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continuously make up for the results of institutionalized discrimination. No action is too small. Try having more racially diverse friends–did you know 75% of white Americans have only white friends? Try sponsoring a black student–did you know fewer than 10% of black over-25s completed a bachelor’s degree?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The police violence must stop. So must the protesters’ violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Train the police better–Did you know over 30 states conduct little-to-none de-escalation training? Every American must know that a highly strict firearm ownership policy throughout the nation will reshape the policing procedures. It will be less necessary for police to be extremely cautious and carry lethal weapons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever your skin color is, before you set a shop on fire, stop to comment on this post and explain how it would help anyone. Because I don’t see your point. Whenever you want to make a point, make sure you know what your point is and learn how to make your point loud and clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what it takes to eradicate racism. I don’t even know if it’s possible. I only know we all must do something to help. I am doing my part. How are you going to help?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">“History will have to record that the greatest tragedy of this period of social transition was not the strident clamor of the bad people, but the appalling silence of the good people.” ― Martin Luther King Jr.</summary></entry></feed>